deepart.io 2016-11-07

# Privacy policy

General Information

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Deepart.io website. You can register a free account which enables you to use Services as defined in Terms and Conditions. The types of personal information collected on the registration page are:

## Email address  

Your email address, and any other information you provide are held in strict confidence. Your information only for the functionality of the Service, including:

  * Confirming your identity,

  * Contacting you whenever the submission is finished,

  * Informing you about news concerning the Service,

  * Informing you about changes in the Service,

  * Informing you about changes in Terms and Conditions.

## IP Addresses

IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in our user registration database when you register with Deepart.io. IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including:

  * To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific company or ISP.

  * To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information  derived from your IP address. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.

  * To estimate the total number of users visiting Deepart.io from specific     geographical regions.

  * To make sure that people are not voting for themselves or friends during contests or promotions.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

  * You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

  * If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Deepart.io products or services that require you to "log in", and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Deepart.io service.

  * Deepart.io uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

    * Access your information when you "log in".

    * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Deepart.io 's services.

    * Display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on Deepart.io.

    * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.

    * Conduct research to improve Deepart.io 's content and services.

Deepart.io lets other companies (such as Google, that show advertisements on some of our pages) set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to Deepart.io 's cookies.

## Information sharing and disclosure

We use email addresses for Services. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

When you publish a picture, your picture is visible to other users.

If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Deepart.io does not rent or sell your personal information.

Finally, we never use or share the personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except to provide products or services which you have requested.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Deepart.io may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information, we will place a prominent notice on our site.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at admin@deepart.io
